Siddhant Jain

Pune, Maharashtra, India



jainsiddhant1608@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/siddhant-jain-08976b19b

Summary

Creative and self-motivated professional with a passion for technologies. Interested into Web Development and IOT. Well versed into python programming. Energetic and friendly worker who is quick to learn new skills while providing the highest standard of work. A dedicated and determined individual who excels under pressure, enjoys working with others or independently. Experience working, both individually and as part of a team

Experience



🛌 Full Stack Developer

ShapeAl

Jul 2021 - Present (2 months +)

internship IoT Intern

Internship studio May 2021 - Jun 2021 (2 months)

Education



Pimpri Chinchwad College of Engineering and Research

Bachelor in Engineering, Electronics and Telecommunication Engineering 2018 - 2022

ALLEN CAREER INSTITUTE

JEE

May 2016 - Feb 2018

Deogiri College Aurangabad

Higher Secondary Schooling, Science May 2016 - May 2018



PSBA English School

High School, 10th std Jul 2011 - Feb 2016

Licenses & Certifications

Introduction to Web Development - University of California, Davis

C6GLMZTDNVRP

- Aptitude National Engineering Olympiad NEO4-10139
- Learn to Design your Own Solar Home System Energy Swaraj Foundation 1ss-w_35955
- **EnglishScore** British Council Issued Jul 2020 Expires Jul 2021 ce105ade
- Internship in Internet of Things Internship studio
 ISIOTI5004

Skills

HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Internet of Things (IoT) • Web Development • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Data Structures • Python (Programming Language) • GitHub • C • Time Management

Honors & Awards

Certificate of Excellence - National Engineering Olympiad

Aug 2021

Achieved an All India Rank 42 in National Engineering Olympiad 4.0 which was conducted in July 2021